# UTHAMAN.K.KUTTAN UI / UX DESIGNER AND FRONTEND DEVELOPER

I have 5 years of experience in Web and Graphic industry. Since, last 4 years, I am doing UI/UX designs and front-end development. I am well versed in Adobe Creative Suite 6, CSS3, HTML 5 and capable of editing JQuery, JavaScript and up to certain good limit. And, I can build 100% responsive website.









### **EDUCATION**

Diploma in Visual Media from ARENA MULTIMEDIA , Thrissur.

High School Education from Holy Cross High School, Thrissur

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2013 - present

Alwafaagroup
Senior Webdesigner

2011- 2013

Infocom Software Pvt. Ltd
Senior Webdesigner

2010 - 2011

WebCastle Media Pvt LTD

Junior Webdesigner

— SKILLS —











HTML5

CSS3

Jquery

## — PERSONAL PROFILE —

Date of Birth 21th May, 1985

Languages Known Tamil, Malayalam and English

Nationality Indian

Marital Status Single

Gender Male

Passport No. K3886974

Visa Status Employment Visa

## — HOBBIES & ACTIVITIES —







Muvies



Songs



Drewing